asa_questions = [
    {
        "question": "A network analyst wants to monitor the activity of all new interns. Which type of security testing would track when the interns sign on and sign off the network?",
        "options": [
            "a) vulnerability scanning",
            "b) password cracking",
            "c) network scanning",
            "d) integrity checker"
        ],
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a characteristic of SIEM?",
        "options": [
            "a) can be implemented as software or as a service",
            "b) Microsoft port scanning tool designed for Windows",
            "c) uses penetration testing to determine most network vulnerabilities",
            "d) provides real-time reporting for short-term security event analysis"
        ],
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "What testing tool is available for network administrators who need a GUI version of Nmap?",
        "options": [
            "a) SuperScan",
            "b) SIEM",
            "c) Nessus",
            "d) Zenmap"
        ],
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the goal of network penetration testing?",
        "options": [
            "a) determining the feasibility and the potential consequences of a successful attack",
            "b) detecting potential weaknesses in systems",
            "c) detecting configuration changes on network systems",
            "d) detecting weak passwords"
        ],
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which instance will traffic be denied as it crosses the ASA 5505 device?",
        "options": [
            "a) traffic originating from the inside network going to the DMZ network",
            "b) traffic originating from the inside network going to the outside network",
            "c) traffic originating from the outside network going to the DMZ network",
            "d) traffic originating from the outside network going to the inside network"
        ],
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "What can be configured as part of a network object?",
        "options": [
            "a) interface type",
            "b) IP address and mask",
            "c) upper layer protocol",
            "d) source and destination MAC address"
        ],
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "How does network scanning help assess operations security?",
        "options": [
            "a) It can detect open TCP ports on network systems.",
            "b) It can detect weak or blank passwords.",
            "c) It can simulate attacks from malicious sources.",
            "d) It can log abnormal activity."
        ],
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the function of a policy map configuration when an ASA firewall is being configured?",
        "options": [
            "a) binding a service policy to an interface",
            "b) binding class maps with actions",
            "c) identifying interesting traffic",
            "d) using ACLs to match traffic"
        ],
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of configuring an IP address on an ASA device in transparent mode?",
        "options": [
            "a) management",
            "b) routing",
            "c) NAT",
            "d) VPN connectivity"
        ],
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which license provides up to 50 IPsec VPN users on an ASA 5506-X device?",
        "options": [
            "a) the most commonly pre-installed Base license",
            "b) a purchased Security Plus upgrade license",
            "c) a purchased Base license",
            "d) a purchased AnyConnect Premium license"
        ],
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "What mechanism is used by an ASA device to allow inspected outbound traffic to return to the originating sender who is on an inside network?",
        "options": [
            "a) access control lists",
            "b) Network Address Translation",
            "c) security zones",
            "d) stateful packet inspection"
        ],
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "When configuring interfaces on an ASA, what piece of information must be included?",
        "options": [
            "a) group association",
            "b) service level",
            "c) FirePower version",
            "d) name",
        ],
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "When configuring interfaces on an ASA, is there another piece of information that must be included?",
        "options": [
            "a) group association",
            "b) service level",
            "c) FirePower version",
            "d) access list",
            "e) security level"
        ],
        "answer": "e"
    },
    {
        "question": "What interface configuration command is used on an ASA to request an IP address from an upstream DSL device?",
        "options": [
            "a) ip address ip-address netmask",
            "b) ip address dhcp setroute",
            "c) dhcpd address IP_address1 [ -IP_address2 ] if_name",
            "d) ip address pppoe"
        ],
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the Tripwire network testing tool?",
        "options": [
            "a) to perform vulnerability scanning",
            "b) to provide information about vulnerabilities and aid in penetration testing and IDS signature development",
            "c) to assess configuration against established policies, recommended best practices, and compliance standards",
            "d) to detect unauthorized wired network access",
            "e) to provide password auditing and recovery"
        ],
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "A network analyst is testing the security of the systems and networks of a corporation. What tool could be used to audit and recover passwords?",
        "options": [
            "a) L0phtCrack",
            "b) SuperScan",
            "c) Nessus",
            "d) Metasploit"
        ],
        "answer": "a"
    }
]
